Robertson Lovell McClure

May 14th, 2016

(647) 229-4608 r.mcclure@mail.utoronto.ca

robertsonmcclure.ca

I am a third year student-athlete at the University of Toronto pursuing a Major in Mathematics and a Specialist's Degree in Computer Science. When I'm not being paid to develop software, or paying to learn about developing software, you can find me reading books about software.

Skills

Python Java C HTML/CSS JavaScript SVN Git Vim

Employment

Software Developer

StockRender

Summer of 2016

• Develop an API for the terminal, a product StockRender sells to hedge funds.

Sports Analytics Developer

UofT Strength & Conditioning Summer of 2016

• Create a database to store Strength Data and automate the processing of daily survey results

Head Referee / Convener

UofT Intramural Volleyball

2015 - Present

• Hire, train and schedule volleyball officials for the 10+ matches that occur every weekday

Recruiting Assistant

UofT Mens Volleyball

2015 - Present

• Facilitate campus tours to potential recruits, communicate with all athletes who are interested in being recruited and assist recruits in navigating UofT's application process

Statistician

UofT Mens Volleyball

2014 - Present

2012 - Present

• Scout opponents using Data Project Software and report in-game statistics to coaching staff

Certified Volleyball Official

Ontario Volleyball Association

- Ensure that match play occurs in accordance to Volleyball Canada Rules
- Apply interpretation of rules to in-game scenarios

Mathematics Tutor

Self-Employed

2014 - 2015

- Teach first year calculus and linear algebra in a comprehensive manner
- Create individualized lesson plan for each student to cater to their needs

Counsellor

Camp Tawingo

2013 - 2015

- Responsible for 8 ten year old boys at over night camp for their three week stay
- Organize themed programs and games for campers

Volunteer Positions

Website Administrator & Videographer The Reading Line

2015 - Present

- Update TheReadingLine.ca and design the user experience as the web-traffic increases
- Create promotional videos, which includes directing, producing, filming and editing.

Sitting Volleyball Data Entry Volunteer Parapan American Games Summer of 2015

• Use volleyball terminology to translate the game into live statistics in a fast paced environment

Volleyball Data Entry Volunteer Pan American Games Summer of 2015

• Use volleyball terminology to translate the game into live statistics in a fast paced environment

Creative Director 100in1day | Slow Down Jane Summer of 2015

- Create promotional videos, which includes directing, producing, filming and editing.
- Advise on outreach plans to local communities

Elected Positions

Athlete and Team Manager

UofT Mens Volleyball

2014 - Present

- Commit over two hours every day to the team
- Responsible for the team's equipment including the camera, food supplements, etc.
- Prompt execution of miscellaneous jobs at the discretion of the Head Coach

Gate House President

Victoria College

2015 - Present

- Organize social events including a Pub Night and Traditional Ceremonies
- Represent the needs of Gate House at the Building Council Meetings

Math Union Treasurer

University of Toronto

2015 - Present

- Responsible for the allocation of funds and balancing the budget
- Reimburse Math Union members for approved purchases and manage the bank account

Math Union Social Officer

University of Toronto

2014 - 2015

- Organize catered social events in conjuncture with other unions
- Responsible for acquiring and transporting food to and from the venue

Athletic Representative

Gate House Council

2014 - 2015

- Advertise Varsity Athletics to Gate House
- · Assist in organizing athletic events for Gate House Members

Athletic Banquet Coordinator

UTS Athletics

2014

- Organize a 3 hour catered award event that featured multiple key note speakers
- Master of Ceremonies

Volleyball Coach

UTS Athletics

2011 - 2014

• Plan practices, coach volleyball and travel with the team to tournaments

Education

| B.Sc. Math B.Sc. Computer Science Ontario Secondary School Diploma Awards | University of Toronto University of Toronto University of Toronto Schools | Class of 2019 Class of 2019 Class of 2014 |
|---|---|---|
| Dean's Leadership Scholar Award | Faculty of Kinesiology | 2016 |
| Professor R. K. Arnold Scholarship Regents Admissions Scholarship Presidents Entrance Scholarship | Victoria University Victoria University University of Toronto | 2015 2014 2014 |
| University of Toronto Schools Diploma Ontario Scholar | University of Toronto Schools University of Toronto Schools | 2014 2014 |